scaryforkids.com 2018-01-07

# 

    Privacy Policy for ScaryForKids.com
    
    Whenever you visit any website on the Internet, some information is exchanged. 
    The privacy of our visitors to ScaryForKids.com is important to us. 
    We recognize that privacy of your personal information is important. 
    For this reason, we do not look at or use any personal information when you 
    visit ScaryForKids.com. We would never sell your personal information to third parties.
    
    Log Files
    Some websites collect and use the data contained in log files.  
    The information in the log files include  your IP (internet protocol) address, 
    your ISP, the browser you used to visit our site, the time you visited the site 
    and which pages you visited throughout the site. 
    At ScaryForKids.com, we do not look at or use this information.
    
    Cookies and Web Beacons
    We do not use cookies to store information, 
    such as your personal preferences when you visit our site.
    
    We only use Google advertisements on ScaryForKids.com 
    because we regard Google as a trustworthy company.  
    Google may use technology such as cookies and web beacons 
    when they advertise on our site, which will also send Google 
    information including your IP address, your ISP , the browser 
    you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have 
    Flash installed.  This is generally used for geotargeting purposes 
    (showing New York real estate ads to someone in New York, for example) 
    or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited 
    (such as showing cooking ads to someone who frequents cooking sites).
    
    DoubleClick DART cookies
    Google may also use DART cookies for ad serving through Google’s DoubleClick, which places a cookie on your computer when you are browsing the web 
    and visit a site using DoubleClick advertising (including some Google advertisements).  
    This cookie is used to serve ads specific to you and your interests.  
    The ads served will be targeted based on your previous browsing history.
    DART uses “non personally identifiable information”.  
    It does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, 
    email address, physical address, telephone number, social security numbers, bank account numbers or credit card numbers.  You can opt-out of 
    this ad serving on all sites using this advertising by visiting 
    http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/dart_adserving.aspx  
    
    You can chose to disable or selectively turn off cookies in your 
    browser settings, or by managing preferences in your Internet Security program.  
    However, this can affect how you are able to interact with some websites. 
    This could include the inability to login to services or programs, 
    such as logging into forums or accounts.
    
    Deleting cookies does not mean you are permanently opted out of any advertising program. Unless you have settings that disallow cookies, the next time you visit a site running the advertisements, a new cookie will be added.
    
    Third-Parties and Your Ad Choices
    
    Third parties may collect information about you through the Services, including through use of the technologies described above. We may not have access to, nor control over, these third parties' data collection practices and we do not assume any liability related to their collection or use.
    
    For instance, in addition to our own systems, we may use DoubleClick, DoubleClick Mobile, Google, Google AdMob, nRelate (which is an affiliate of About, Inc.) and other third-party Ad Servers and data management platforms to serve and display Advertisements. They may use cookies, pixel trackers, or other internet or mobile technology to collect non-personal and/or anonymous information about your use of the Services. In certain cases, you have options and choices about the collection and use of information by third parties on our Websites:
    •For more information about these third-party Ad Networks and opting out of tracking, see: http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp.
    •For more information about interest-based advertising and opting out, see: http://www.aboutads.info/choices/
    •For more information about disabling and controlling third-party cookies in your browser, see: http://www.aboutcookies.org/Default.aspx?page=1
    •For more information on nRelate and opting out of browser history tracking, see: http://nrelate.com/privacy-policy/
    
    In addition to Ad Servers and data management platforms, other third parties, including analytics services providers and companies with whom we have affiliate or linking agreements, may collect information about you directly through the Services. They may use cookies, pixel trackers, or other internet technology to collect non-personal information about your use of the Services. They may use this information to show you ads on other Web sites based on your demonstrated interests, or in some cases, your location.
    
    If you require more information or have questions about our privacy policy, you can contact us by email at scaryforkids (at) yahoo.com
